[{"question": " oh! hey, rach!", "answer": " hi! hey, happy valentine&#146;s day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh, you, too.", "answer": " hey, so, uh, how&#146;s it going living over at ross&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " it&#146;s good. except he makes us watch the discovery channel all day long. did you know that something really boring happened to someone really ugly in the middle ages?  oh, thank you. i&#146;ll see you guys later.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " there&#146;s one lucky to-go cup of coffee.", "answer": "  honey, i wish you would get over her. i hate seeing you like this. is there anything i can do for you? do you want to look down my top?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " thanks. but maybe later.", "answer": " oh, gunther, can i get a scone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  you want anything?", "answer": " you know what i want? i want a lot of things! i want to be with the woman i love on valentine&#146;s day! and i want her to love me back! and i want just one moment of relief from the gut-wrenching pain of knowing that that&#146;s never going to happen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " we have red bagels.", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " so, how does mona feel about you and rachel living together?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m actually on my way to tell her right now. yeah, she&#146;s been away all week visiting her parents, but she&#146;ll be cool. i mean, she&#146;s been so supportive. she-she even got the baby a tiny t-shirt that says, &#145;fossils are my friends.&#146;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " ugh. come on, mona, don&#146;t kiss ass.", "answer": " uh, i&#146;m going to take off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " all right. oh! shoot! oh shoot! uh, rachel wanted to see this tape!", "answer": " what is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " it&#146;s a video of my friend giving birth. could you just bring it back to your apartment?", "answer": " all right.  &#145;candy and cookie?&#146;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah. candy&#146;s the mother, cookie&#146;s the daughter. the father&#146;s also cookie. why am i friends with these people?", "answer": "  phoebe, c&#146;mere. i want to show you something in the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, monica, grow up!", "answer": " hey, what&#146;s behind your back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " nothing. just something i want to get phoebe&#146;s opinion on for valentine&#146;s day.", "answer": " you don&#146;t want my opinion?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " not really.", "answer": " come on, i&#146;m your older brother, ask me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " all right, big brother.  which of these do you think would make your little sister look hotter, so your best friend would want to do her?", "answer": "  the red one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hey. look, i know you&#146;ve been really depressed lately, so i brought someone over to cheer you up. right outside this door is a real, live, furry playmate.", "answer": " no, i&#146;m not sleeping with your friend jane again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " he-hee!", "answer": " hey! a dog! hi! who, you got to admit, looks a lot like jane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " this is the happiest dog in the world. i borrowed him from my friend wendy. now, you can only keep him until he cheers you up. and he will cheer you up!", "answer": " thanks so much, pheebs!  we are going to have so much fun, yes we are!  oh! not that kind of fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " happy valentine&#146;s!", "answer": "  okay! i&#146;ll be right out. i&#146;m slipping into something a little less comfortable, and a little more slutty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  &#145;candy and cookie&#146;. &#145;candy and cookie?&#146; monica got me porn?! girl-on-girl porn?! she really must love me!!   man on tv: yeah, just relax.", "answer": " i love you, st. valentine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " woah, woah, that&#146;s not pretty! man on tv: now, push! woman on tv: ow! ow! ooh! that hurts!", "answer": " worst porn ever! worst porn ever!  woman on tv: ohhh! make it stop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  did i just throw this?", "answer": "  hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " i accidentally packed these with my stuff.  who is this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh, that&#146;s, uh, that&#146;s phoebe&#146;s friend&#146;s dog. i don&#146;t know what his real name is, but i call him mozzarella.", "answer": "  oh, well, you are so cute! i wish i could play with you more, but i&#146;ve got to go to work! i hope i stop talking like this before my marketing meeting, yes i do. yes i do.  bye-bye, joey. oh, i seriously can&#146;t stop it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  i&#146;ve still got it!", "answer": "  why did you get me this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what is it?", "answer": " it&#146;s yelling&#133;bleeding&#133;dilating. oh, the dilating&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " is this the video of the baby being born? sweetie, this is phoebe&#146;s. why were you even watching it?", "answer": " i thought&#133;maybe&#133;you got me porn for valentine&#146;s day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " chandler, if you thought i was going to get you porn for valentine&#146;s day&#133;  you were right! apparently, it&#146;s about a young girl who moves to the big city, you know, in search of stardom, but ends up having sex with a lot of guys! yeah, it got four starts!  oh, wait a minute. those aren&#146;t stars. anyway, you want to take a look?", "answer": " well, i&#146;m not really in a sexy mood right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " honey, what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " well, remember the first time we saw jaws?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " mm-hmm.", "answer": " how long it took to go back in the water?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " chandler, we can&#146;t let this tape wreck valentine&#146;s day!", "answer": " you don&#146;t know. you didn&#146;t see it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " child-birth, it&#146;s a natural thing! it&#146;s beautiful.", "answer": " oh, beautiful? really? beautiful? you think this is beautiful?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh! oh, my god! no wonder my mother hates me!", "answer": " see, honey, there&#146;s&#151;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!  so, how was atlantic city?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " good.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i brought you back a present.", "answer": " wha&#151;? oh, come on. you didn&#146;t have to&#151;saltwater taffy?!  thanks! this is interesting. you know, most people think this is made with sea water, but it&#146;s actually made with, uh, salted fresh water. that&#146;s not interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " i think it&#146;s interesting.", "answer": " i do too! i missed you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i missed you, too! so, how was your week?", "answer": " oh, it was good! it was good. actually, the baby started kicking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " how exciting!", "answer": " yeah! i know! it was. oh&#133; the only sad thing is i wasn&#146;t around when it happened for the first time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh no.", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m missing out on all this other stuff, too. so, joey suggested rachel move in with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  yeah right!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  huh&#133;uh-huh.", "answer": " huh, could you imagine. i go away for a few days, and come back, and my boyfriend is living with some woman he got pregnant!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " so, what&#146;d you tell him?", "answer": "  just a second!  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " how could you not tell mona that rachel is living with you?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, she seemed to think it was such a crazy idea! um, plus, she, uh, she got me taffy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " taffy, really? i&#146;ve never had any.", "answer": " ever?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " well, i think my mother was too busy planning her suicide to provide saltwater treats.  thank you! so what, you&#146;re just never going to tell her?", "answer": " oh, no, no, no, i will! i just want to butter her up, first! you know, i&#146;m going to take her to an amazing valentine&#146;s dinner. do all this romantic stuff, and then, just when she thinks i&#146;m the best boyfriend in the world, then i&#146;m going to tell her that my pregnant ex-girlfriend is living with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " so, between her and me being friends, and her history with ross, it just isn&#146;t going to happen. it would be like you falling in love with a cat.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey, buddy. how&#146;s my favorite dog, huh? how&#146;s my favorite dog?  you&#146;re subdued.  did you give him a beer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " will you excuse us, we need to talk for a moment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " he&#146;s miserable! what happened to him?", "answer": " nothing. we just talked about stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " what stuff?", "answer": " rachel stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh&#133;joey, you bummed him out! this was the happiest dog in the world, and he spends half a day with you, and look at him!", "answer": " he&#146;s breathing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " okay, i&#146;m going to take him back to wendy&#146;s.", "answer": " no, no, no, no! he&#146;s fine! look, look, look!  here&#146;s your ball! get your ball! get your ball!  get your ball! my god, what have i done to you, huh? i broke the dog! pheebs, i broke the dog!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " well, i&#146;m, uh, going to pick up mona. what have you got going tonight?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;ve got big valentine&#146;s plans! i&#146;ve got my chinese food on the way, and the rest of your saltwater taffy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " y&#146;know, it&#146;s interesting! most people think that&#146;s made with seawater, when in fact&#151;", "answer": " ross, we actually watched the documentary together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  mona? what are&#151;hi! what are you doing here? i&#146;m, um, supposed to pick you up!", "answer": " change of plans, i made you a special valentine&#146;s dinner! surprise!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ayyyayyyy!", "answer": "  oh, hey, mona!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " hi! hi. hi, rachel!  what&#146;s she doing here?", "answer": " i have no idea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " seriously, what is she doing?", "answer": " uh&#133;lately, she just likes hanging out here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " i think she&#146;s lonely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " okay, but it&#146;s valentine&#146;s day!", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " can&#146;t we just ask her to go?", "answer": " no, no. she&#146;s way to emotional. and by emotional i mean crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i&#146;m not here! that&#146;s just my chinese food!", "answer": " oh, my god! she has food delivered here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " mm-hmm. she&#146;s&#151;she&#146;s emotional, but, but ballsy.", "answer": " you know what i&#146;m going to do? i&#146;m going to get in my sweats, and eat this in bed!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " and you thought she was going to be in our way! so, why don&#146;t you, uh, open the champagne, and i&#146;ll be right back. i&#146;ve got a surprise for you.", "answer": " you got another ex-wife back there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  i&#146;m just going to grab the phone.", "answer": " oh, rachel! wait! hey, i hope you don&#146;t take this the wrong way, but, but, um&#133; what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, i&#146;m sorry! do you need the phone?", "answer": " no, no. listen, ross is too nice to say anything, but this is his apartment, and, and, we gotta have some boundaries, so why don&#146;t you go back to your place and give us some privacy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  but, but, mona, i live here.", "answer": "  happy valentine&#146;s day! &#133;or something to remember me by.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " how long has it been this time?", "answer": " 90 seconds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " that&#146;s better. 90 seconds is a long time not to think about it&#133;except all i did was think about it.", "answer": " you know, it haunts me? up &#145;til now, the worst thing i ever saw, was my father doing tequila shots off the naked houseboy. after this, i would gladly make that my screensaver!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " okay, well, we have to get past this! why don&#146;t we get rid of the tape and pretend it never existed?", "answer": " i can do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oh, thank god!", "answer": " oh, i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " come in!", "answer": "  hi! i&#146;m so sorry to barge in on your valentine&#146;s, but i had to get away from all the yelling. mona is dumping ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh, my god.", "answer": " poor ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh, great. we have to watch him do yoga in his underwear, but for this he closes the drapes!", "answer": " rach, you know that birthing tape you wanted to see? it&#146;s here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh, and we should warn you, before you watch it: don&#146;t watch it.", "answer": " why? you saw it? is it scary?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, let&#146;s just say it&#146;s ironic how footage of someone being born can make you want to kill yourself.", "answer": " well, now, wait. now i&#146;m all freaked out. come on, you guys will watch it with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no, but i will leave a sweater that smells like me right next to you!", "answer": " c&#146;mon, seriously, you guys, you&#146;re not going to make me watch this alone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " she&#146;s right&#133;of course not. honey, get the tape.", "answer": "  this reminds me of a very specific part of the tape.  okay, here we go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " okay.  ooh, my!  woah! why is that baby torturing that woman?!", "answer": " why have i seen this thing three times?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it&#146;s&#133;still beautiful.", "answer": " uh! it&#146;s horrible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i know! i know, i&#146;m so sorry for you!", "answer": " oh, my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " wait, you guys, look!", "answer": " what? did her ass explode?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, the baby&#146;s out! look, look!", "answer": " oh, look at those little fingers and toes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " and look how happy the mom is now!", "answer": " oh&#133;rach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " hey, hey, man!", "answer": " hey, what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " uh&#133;mona just dumped me.", "answer": " oh, man, i&#146;m sorry. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " well, with everything that&#146;s been going on lately, i haven&#146;t exactly been the perfect boyfriend. you know, i, uh, i didn&#146;t tell her i got rachel pregnant. i gave her a key to my apartment, and then had the locks changed! and then i lied to her about rachel moving in with me. in a way, i actually judge her for not breaking up with me sooner, you know?", "answer": " still, that really sucks, man. especially on valentine&#146;s day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah. wait a minute. what are you doing here? joey tribbiani without a date on valentine&#146;s day? what&#146;s going on, huh? girl trouble?", "answer": " sort of.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " you don&#146;t have to seem so happy about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh, sorry. well, look, maybe i can help you with it.", "answer": " oh, i&#133;i d&#151;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " anyway, so, uh, so what is it?", "answer": " forget about it. it&#146;s no big deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " c&#146;mon! joey! what is it?", "answer": " it&#146;s nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " hey, hey, it&#146;s me. why can&#146;t you tell me?", "answer": " okay, uh&#133;sit down.  um&#133; there&#146;s this woman that i like. a lot. but, uh&#133;it can&#146;t happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " she&#146;s not a tribbiani?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i knew it. so, is she someone from work?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " well, uh, does she like you?", "answer": " sometimes i think maybe she could. but it doesn&#146;t matter, because i can&#146;t do anything about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " well, it&#146;s complicated. she&#146;s with this other guy. for a long time. someone from work, too. and i could never do that to the guy, because we&#146;re really good friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " so, uh, this guy, she used to go out with, is, uh&#133; is he still in love with her?", "answer": " no. i don&#146;t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " okay. um&#133; is he a good guy?", "answer": " yeah, he&#146;s the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " then talk to him! he might be fine with it.", "answer": " oh, i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " joey, it&#146;s worth finding out. i mean, if you really like her.", "answer": " i do! so much! i can&#146;t stop thinking about her! i can&#146;t sleep, i&#151;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " okay, joey, you know what? you have to go for it. how often does this happen to you, huh? you owe it to yourself.", "answer": "  here&#146;s your warm milk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i&#146;m going to&#133;uh&#133;i&#146;m going to, um, put the bourbon in it at home.", "answer": " oh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}]